#### Contact

9500764836 (Mobile) kathirvarshan2806@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kathirvarshans-b13ab01ba (LinkedIn) kathirvarshan007.github.io/ personalwebsite/ (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

C (Programming Language)
Python (Programming Language)
MATLAB

### Languages

Tamil (Native or Bilingual) English (Limited Working)

# KATHIRVARSHAN S

Tech Enthusiast | Frontend Web Developer |  $\alpha$  - MLSA 21 | LinkedIn Content Administrator - Students for Students Team Sathyamangalam

## Summary

Kathirvarshan is a second year Electrical Engineering student with passion towards coding and technology. I have an experience with software such as Matlab (both coding as well as simulink), Autocad and Proteus. I learnt few programming languages namely C and python.

## Experience

Microsoft
Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador
July 2021 - Present (1 month)

CodeChef BIT Chapter Technical Content Creator May 2020 - June 2021 (1 year 2 months)

The role of the Technical Content creator is to teach programming to the CodeChef community members, providing them a daily challenges and helping them to solve the challenge.

### Education

Bannari Amman Institute of Technology

B.E, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2019 - 2023)